Bah.
باه.
Su Ziying,
سو تسي يينغ ،
how weak you were!
كم كنت ضعيفا!
Why did you just let her spill the water on you?
لماذا تركتها تسكب الماء عليك؟
What else could I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل غير ذلك؟
Pull her hair or slap her?
شد شعرها أو صفعها؟
After all, she said she was Ye Juncheng's fiancée.
بعد كل شيء ، قالت إنها كانت خطيبة يي جونتشنغ.
Bah!
باه!
Why did you trust her?
لماذا وثقت بها؟
An ugly girl like her just came to make trouble.
فتاة قبيحة مثلها أتت للتو لإثارة المشاكل.
You didn't see her.
لم ترها.
How do you know she's ugly?
كيف تعرف انها قبيحة؟
All girls
كل الفتيات
who play dirty tricks
الذين يلعبون الحيل القذرة
are either ugly or malicious.
إما أن تكون قبيحة أو خبيثة.
By the way,
على فكرة،
you and Ye Juncheng kissed several times.
أنت و Ye Juncheng قبلتم عدة مرات.
You should have been in a relationship.
كان يجب أن تكون في علاقة.
Based on my experience from 102 Korean dramas
بناء على تجربتي من 102 دراما كورية
and my first love,
وحبي الأول ،
nothing in love should be delayed.
لا شيء في الحب يجب أن يتأخر.
Your first love?
حبك الاول؟
When did you and Lin Han
متى أنت ولين هان
start a relationship?
بدء علاقة؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
But soon, I guess.
لكن سرعان ما أعتقد.
Su Ziying,
سو تسي يينغ ،
don't interrupt.
لا تقاطع.
We're talking about your problem.
نحن نتحدث عن مشكلتك.
When will you be in a relationship with him?
متى ستكون على علاقة معه؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
Then go ask him.
ثم اذهب واسأله.
A girl of the new era
فتاة العصر الجديد
should be active
يجب أن تكون نشطة
and daring in love.
وجرأة في الحب.
Go. Go right away.
يذهب.  اذهب على الفور.
=My Honey=
= حبيبي =
=EP15 Misunderstood or Flipped=
= EP15 يساء فهمه أو مقلوب =
There you are.
ها أنت ذا.
Juncheng, what makes you so happy?
Juncheng ، ما الذي يجعلك سعيدا جدا؟
I knew you cared for me.
علمت أنك تهتم بي.
Why is it you?
لماذا انت
How did you come in?
كيف دخلت؟
Your mother told me
قالت لي والدتك
the password to your door, of course.
كلمة السر لبابك بالطبع.
I don't care how you got in.
لا يهمني كيف دخلت.
Get out immediately.
اخرج على الفور.
Oh, dear.
يا عزيزي.
You know.
أنت تعرف.
I just came back to China
لقد عدت للتو إلى الصين
and I have nowhere to live.
وليس لدي مكان أعيش فيه.
See? I've brought my luggage.
نرى؟  لقد أحضرت أمتعتي.
I can book a hotel room for you.
يمكنني حجز غرفة فندق لك.
No. I want to stay here.
لا ، أريد أن أبقى هنا.
Ye Juncheng...
يي جونتشنغ ...
Juncheng, I said I could carry the luggage myself.
Juncheng ، قلت إن بإمكاني حمل الأمتعة بنفسي.
Sorry to have interrupted you.
آسف لمقاطعتك.
Su Ziying!
سو تسى يينغ!
(Girls' Dormitory)
(عنبر البنات)
(Girls' Dormitory No admission for Boys)
(سكن البنات ممنوع الدخول للبنين)
This is the Girls' Dormitory.
هذا هو عنبر البنات.
You mustn't come in.
لا يجب أن تدخل.
Come on.
هيا.
Su Ziying misunderstood me.
لقد أساءت Su Ziying فهمي.
I have to explain to her.
علي أن أشرح لها.
Well, well,
حسنا حسنا،
I guess someone should solve his problem first.
أعتقد أن شخصًا ما يجب أن يحل مشكلته أولاً.
Hey, what are you doing here?
مرحبًا ، ماذا تفعل هنا؟
This is the Girls' Dormitory. Go, go, go.
هذا هو عنبر البنات.  إذهب! إذهب! إذهب.
Get out.
اخرج.
Leave immediately.
غادر على الفور.
The game against Zhongyang Academy of Art is a few days away.
المباراة ضد أكاديمية Zhongyang للفنون على بعد أيام قليلة.
We haven't got a point guard yet.
ليس لدينا نقطة حراسة حتى الآن.
Lin Han,
لين هان ،
what do you think we should do?
ماذا تعتقد أنه يجب علينا فعله؟
Shall we
هلا فعلنا
search different grades for one?
البحث عن درجات مختلفة عن واحد؟
Mm.
مم.
We lost to Zhongyang Academy of Art for consecutive years.
خسرنا أمام أكاديمية Zhongyang للفنون لسنوات متتالية.
If we lose again,
إذا خسرنا مرة أخرى ،
what a humiliation it'll be!
يا له من ذل سيكون!
Yeah.
نعم.
Hey.
يا.
Watch out!
احذر!
Lin Han, are you all right?
لين هان ، هل أنت بخير؟
Ye Juncheng?
يي جونتشنغ؟
To what honor do I owe this?
لأي شرف أنا مدين بهذا؟
If you want to see Su Ziying,
إذا كنت تريد رؤية Su Ziying ،
you know what,
أتعلم،
she doesn't want to see you now.
هي لا تريد رؤيتك الآن.
No.
رقم.
I'm here to see you.
أنا هنا لأراك.
Me?
أنا؟
Lin Han,
لين هان ،
do me a favor.
أعمل لي معروفا.
I want to explain to Su Ziying.
أريد أن أشرح لسو زيينغ.
Don't try to play tricks.
لا تحاول أن تلعب الحيل.
I don't buy it.
أنا لا أشتريه.
What do you buy, then?
ماذا تشتري إذن؟
I can do anything.
يمكنني أن أفعل أي شيء.
No, no, no.
لا لا لا.
Stay away from me.
ابق بعيد عني.
I won't sell out my friend for anything.
لن أبيع صديقي مقابل أي شيء.
I just won't.
أنا فقط لن أفعل.
Are you sure?
هل أنت واثق؟
I heard you needed a point guard.
سمعت أنك بحاجة إلى حارس.
Aha.
اها.
You want to pursue Ziying. Count on me.
تريد متابعة Ziying.  اعتمد علي.
(Love mania)
(هوس الحب)
Lin Han,
لين هان ،
I have something to ask you.
لدي شيء أن أسألك.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
When's Su Ziying's birthday?
متى عيد ميلاد Su Ziying؟
Still a long way away.
لا يزال الطريق طويلا.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Zero.
صفر.
Two.
اثنين.
♪My love don't ever leave me♪
♪ حبي لا يتركني أبدًا
Five.
خمسة.
♪Tonight I'll leave an exclusive mark on you♪
♪ الليلة سأترك بصمة حصرية عليك
♪Let's go I plan to sneak into your dream♪
♪ دعنا نذهب وأنا أخطط للتسلل إلى حلمك ♪
♪Turn into the angle and devil and be the only love in your heart♪
♪ استدر إلى الزاوية والشيطان وكن الحب الوحيد في قلبك
♪My love Stay on a tipsy afternoon♪
♪ حبي ابقى في فترة ما بعد الظهيرة
♪The starry sky in midsummer shines for you♪
السماء المرصعة بالنجوم في منتصف الصيف تضيء لك
♪You're so perfect my love my love♪
♪ أنت مثالي جدًا حبيبي
♪You hug me and get no longer defensive♪
أنت تعانقني ولم تعد دفاعيًا ♪
♪I hide the roses behind me♪
♪ أخفي الورود خلفي ♪
(All rights of network communication reserved by Tencent)
(جميع حقوق اتصالات الشبكة محفوظة لشركة Tencent)